Guide to the Richard Hell Papers 1944-2003 (Bulk 1969-2003) MSS.140
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Subseries A: Journals and Notebooks
    - Journal 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Journal 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Materials from Journal 80-83, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Materials Copied from Journals, 1974-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Journal 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Materials from Journal 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Blue Notebook 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Notebook Paris and N. O. 83-84, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Materials from Notebook, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Notebook 1984 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1984 Notebook: Poetry (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1984 Notebook: Band (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1984 Notebook: Misc (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Journal 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Journal 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Materials from Journal 1986 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Ledger Notebook, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Materials from Ledger, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Black and Red Journal, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Journals Book II, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1987 Journal (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Materials from 1987 Journal (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Heroin in London Notebook, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Blue Notebook 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Orange Notebook 1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Record Notebook 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Materials from Record Notebook, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Red Notebook, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Computer Journal Print Out, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Red Notebook 1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Journal Materials 1988-90, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Pink Notebook 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Notebook 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Plaid Notebook 1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Orange Notebook 1990 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Computer Journal June-November, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Notepad 1991 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Composition Book 1991 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Turtle Notebook, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Small Notebook, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Green Notebook, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Japanese Notebook, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Dim Star Music Notebook, 1990-1992 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Task Notebook, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Notebook 1993-94 or so, ca.1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Memo Book, 1994-1998 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Drive Salt Lake City-LA-SF-Boston, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Notebook 1996 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Journal 1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Memo Book, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Slum Journal/Theresa Interview, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Materials from Slum Journal…, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Slum Journal/Borges Notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Movies, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Anthology of a Polymorphic Soul, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Partial Notebook, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Pages from Unknown Journal, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Subseries B: Sketchbooks
    Richard Hell's sketchbooks. See also Oversize.
    - Red Sketchbook, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Blue Sketchbook, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Materials from Blue Sketchbook, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Sketchbook, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Material from Sketchbook, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Subseries C: Poetry
    Richard Hell's poetry manuscripts, the groupings follow the author's system of categorization.
    - 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - The Drunken Boat collaboration with Tom Verlaine, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Collaborations with Tom Verlaine, undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - 1970-73, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Poems post R'n'R, 1974-1983 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Collaboration with Cookie Mueller and H. M. Koutoukas, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 74*)
    - Collaborations with Patti Smith, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Life Among the Alert of Europe with Cookie Mueller, Oct. 7, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - 1985 to Revise (Box 3, Folder 77*)
    - 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - The Drunken Boat collaboration with Lizzie Mercier, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - 1988-90, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Misc. Poems, undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Misc. manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Homage, impersonations, etc., undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Unrevised Manuscripts, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Duplicates, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Lines, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Poetry File Folder with notes, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Materials from Poetry File Folder, undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Rejected Poetry, undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - rejected for Word Processor, undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Master 1-2-3 plus Mike Collab. 1/2, undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Master 1-2-3 plus Mike Collab. 2/2, undated (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Master 1-2-3, undated (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Subseries D: Prose
    Richard Hell's prose (fiction and non-fiction) manuscripts.
    - The Ramones Mean Business, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Interview w/David Johansen, ca.1976 (Box 4, Folder 94A)
    - David Johansen: Secret Messages, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 94B)
    - Story, early 1978 (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Untitled MS "Before I tried it…", 1978 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - My Way of Life, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Inter-Life Merge Job, 8/30/1979 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Slum Journal Manuscripts, undated (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Slum Journal Envelope with notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Slum Journal: Sex Theme, undated (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Slum Journal #4 MS "Lowest Common Dominator", undated (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - It's All True, undated (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Unrequited Narcissism for Mudd Club Performance, undated (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Notes on Junk/Rock, undated (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Untitled MS "Nothing means as…", undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Life Sucks for High Times, undated (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Peter Schuyff Catalog Text, undated (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Untitled MS "Making love of the…", undated (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Second String Notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - The Reverend Hell Speaks, undated (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Dear Reader, undated (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Untitled Partial Typescript, undated (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Peter Laughner Article and Materials, undated (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Misc. Unclassified Prose, undated (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Fragmentary Interview, undated (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Untitled MS "In May I suddenly…", undated (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Will's Bellyache, undated (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Time for Your Spanking, undated (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Partial MS, undated (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Huckleberry Hell, undated (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Knotty Knotty Boy, undated (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Review of Sonic Youth, Goo, undated (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Collaborations with Mike DeCapite, undated (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Untitled MS "Once upon a time…", undated (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - My Burroughs, undated (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Manhattan Catalogue "Consumer Profile", undated (Box 4, Folder 127A)
  - Subseries E: Film Scripts
    Manuscripts of Richard Hell's film scripts and treatments; produced projects are filed separately by project.
    - Trash Starkweather Treatment, undated (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Sweet Hunk of Trash notes, collab with Nicole Burdette, undated (Box 4, Folder 129)
    - Sweet Hunk of Trash drafts, collab with Nicole Burdette, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Aghast, treatment and outline, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - Tilt-a-whirl, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Untitled treatment, undated (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Subseries F: Music
    Manuscripts of Richard Hell's lyrics, also include set lists and other notes.
    - Early 70s Music Notebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Materials from notebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Voidoid I Lyrics, undated (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Blank Generation Sheet Music, undated (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Record Notebook (Destiny St.), undated (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Notepad, undated (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Blue Lyric Notebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Music Notebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Materials from "Music" Notebook, undated (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Misc. Lyrics 1/2, undated (Box 4, Folder 143*)
    - Misc. Lyrics 2/2, undated (Box 4, Folder 144)
- Series II: Correspondence
  Scope and Content
  Subseries A: Paper-based Correspondence is organized alphabetically by correspondent; correspondence from unidentified or partially identified correspondents is organized by date and follows the last alphabetical entry; a folder containing the early correspondence of Richard Hell's parents (Ernest Meyers and Carolyn Hodgson) annotated by his mother follows and fan mail is collected at the end of the series.
  - Subseries A: Paper Correspondence
    Richard Hell's correspondence, arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
    - Abel, Ann, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Abel, David, undated (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Abrams, Leonard, undated (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Acker, Kathy, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Allan, Nick, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Ambrose, Joe, undated (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Andoh, Chikage, 1989-1993 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Andre, Michael, undated (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - RH to Andrews, Bruce, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - RH to Andrews, Bruce, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Andrews, Bruce, 1973-1979 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Appel, Rosaine, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Arbus, Diane, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Ashe, Lester, undated (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Astor, Pete, undated (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Bachia, Mary Anne, 1982-1996 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Baldwin James, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Bayley, Roberta, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Balfus, Andrea, undated (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Ball, Gordon, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Barker, George, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Barnett, David, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Barth, John, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Barut-Dreuilhe, Kristine, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Baum, Timothy, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Begos, Kevin, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Bennett, Will, undated (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Berc, Shelley, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Berman, Tosh, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Berry, Wendell, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - Beschta, Susan, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Bessy, Claude, undated (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Betrock, Alan, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - Bevan, Sheelagh, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Black, Al, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Black, Noel, undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Bly, Robert, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Bockris, Victor, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Bone, Eugenia, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Bossco, Jean, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Bradbury, Ray, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Breithaupt, Dave, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Brodey, Jim, undated (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - Browne, Kate, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 188)
    - Brown, Lee Ann, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Brownstein, Michael, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Bubush, Nick, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 191)
    - Buckridge, Chris, undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - Bultean, Michel, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Burchill, Brian, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - Burroughs, William, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Cage, John, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Canfield, Debbie and Dan Sawtell, undated (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Carman, Paul, undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Carroll, Dolly (Grandmother), 1989 (Box 5, Folder 198A)
    - Carroll, Paul, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Cartlidge, Katrin, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Cassell, Sandy, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Chernikowski, Stephanie, undated (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Chiarrelle, Gail, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Church, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Clemente, Fauresco, undated (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Coakley, William, undated (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Cohen, Ira, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Cohen, Jessica, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Colebrook, Peter, undated (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Coleman, Elliott, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Coolidge, Clark, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Coolidge, Martha, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Cooper, Dennis, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Cordier, Robert, undated (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Corrdini, Janet, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Curley, Jon, undated (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Dabney, Kathleen, 1976-1997 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Davies, Bevan, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Deasan, Mildred, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Death, Donna, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - DeCapite, Mike, 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - DeCapite, Mike, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - DeCapite, Mike, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - DeCapite, Mike, 1995-2000 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - DeCapite, Mike, undated (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Dermond, Lord Dan, 1992-2000 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Doone, Lorna, undated (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Dougherty, Peter, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - Dricks, Sally, undated (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Drimmer, Jeffrey, undated (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - Duchamp, Marcel, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Duke, Rebecca, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Edmonds, Raf, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Eklund, Lori, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Elvis Presley Museum, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Equi, Elaine, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Eshima, Hiroji, 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Esplen, John (Overground Records), 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Esteban, Michel, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Ezzo, Nanci, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Faber, Mrs. Joel, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Fagin, Larry, undated (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Farmer, Polly, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Faye, Raymond, 1993-2001 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Fields, Walter, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Finley, Ian Hamilton, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Finley, Karen, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Fisher, Joel, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Fisher, Thomas Michael, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Fitzstephens, Stephen, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Flower, Elizabeth, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Ford, Cheryl, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Fox, Hugh, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Friedman, Ed, 1993-2000 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Friedman, Rich, undated (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Froger, Nadine, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Fromberg, Rob, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Fulton, Len, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Gabrieli, Michael, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Gandolf, Victoria, 1981-2001 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Garcia-Villa, Jose, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Gashil, Leila, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Geller, Lynn, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Giannini, David (from), 1967-1972 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Giannini, David (to), 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Giannini, Helen, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Glassgold, Peter, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Godlis, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Goldbarth, Albert, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Goldberg, Jeff, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Goldsworthy, Rupert, 1993-2000 (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Golub, A. Richard, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Gontier, Phillipe, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Gordon, Marsha, 1983-1996 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Görtler, Dirk, 1996-1996 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Gottchrer, Judy and Richard, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Grant, Marni, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Grantier, Bruce, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Graves, Robert, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - Groome, Carle, undated (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Grossman, Richard, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - Gruen, Bob, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - Guccione, Bob, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Harding, Robert, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Harris, Bertha, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Hart, Debbie, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Hart, Fay, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - Hartman, Pat, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Hartman, Yuki, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Haseloff, Charles, undated (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - Hausman, Gerald, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Heffley, Patty, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - Hell, Kyshah, undated (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Hell, Richard (to unidentified correspondents), 1968-1996 (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Hennessey, Marlene, 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Henwood, Simon, undated (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Herbert, Alissa, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Heylin, Clinton, undated (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Hickman, Annie, undated (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Higgins, Dick (Cosmep), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - Hirsh, Richard, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - Hitchcock, Alfred, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Hitchcock, George, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Hobbs, Ronald, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - Hodges, Graham, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - Hodgson, Carolyn (from), 1979-1983 (Box 6, Folder 306A)
    - Hodgson, Carolyn (to), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 306B)
    - Hodgson, Carolyn (MSS from), 1983-1998 (Box 6, Folder 306C)
    - Hostader, Douglas, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Holland, Barbara, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Holland, Sarah, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - Hollander, Kurt (PLES), 1986 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Holman, Bob, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Holt, Mitchell, undated (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - Hopper, John, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - Horstman, Madi, undated (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Hoyt, Heidi, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Huff, William S., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Humphries, J., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Ichihara, Marchiko, undated (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - Isbell, Lori, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - Jackson, Lorri, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Jaffe, Dan, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Johnson, Janice, 1985-1997 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Johnson, Shawn, undated (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Joyce Agency, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 323A)
    - Jud, Reinhard, undated (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Jurek, Thom, undated (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Kaplan, Michael, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - Kaprow, Allen, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - Katz, Eliot, 1982-1996 (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - Katz, Steve, undated (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Katz, Vincent, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Kauf, Pat, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Kelly, Walt, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Kherdian, David, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Klein, Howard, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Knott, Bill, 1970-1991 (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Kolkema, Janette, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - Kornish, Doris, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Kostelanetz, Richard, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Kozic, Maria, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Kraus, Chris, undated (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Kugel, Bernard, undated (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - Kunitz, Stanley, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - Lahey, Frederic and Elizabeth, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Lake, Steve, undated (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Larson, David, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Laughlin, James (from), 1969-1991 (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Laughlin, James (to), 1968-2000 (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Laughner, Peter, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Leaf, June, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - Lee, Annabel, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Lesher, Charlotte and Mickey Leigh, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - Levine, Bob, undated (Box 6, Folder 352)
    - Levitt, Shelley (High Times), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 353)
    - Lole, Cynthia (F-Beat Records), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 354)
    - London, Mel, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 355)
    - Lopez, Ken, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 356)
    - Lopez, Maria Pia, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - Lowe, Nick, undated (Box 6, Folder 358)
    - Lowell, Jim, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 359)
    - Lozada, Sonia, 1981-1984 (Box 6, Folder 360)
    - MacAfee, Norman, undated (Box 6, Folder 361)
    - McKenna, Kristine, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 362)
    - McLaren, Malcolm, undated (Box 6, Folder 363)
    - McNamara, Tom, undated (Box 6, Folder 364)
    - McNeil, Legs, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 365)
    - McNeil, Phil, undated (Box 6, Folder 366)
    - MacShane, Frank, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 367)
    - Madsen, Metti, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 368)
    - Magaziner, D. Arthur, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 369)
    - Marcuse, David, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 370)
    - Marshall, Jim, undated (Box 6, Folder 371)
    - Massee, Kim, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - Mayer, Bernadette, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 373)
    - Mayer, Sandro, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - Mechan, Patricia, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 375)
    - Mercier, Lizzie (from), 1983-2000 (Box 6, Folder 376)
    - Mercier, Lizzie (to), undated (Box 6, Folder 377)
    - Merton, Thomas, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 378)
    - Metz, Michael, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 379)
    - Mesmer, Sharon, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 380)
    - Meyer, James, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 381)
    - Meyers, Babette, 1971-1998 (Box 6, Folder 382)
    - Meyers, Frederic, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 383)
    - Meyers, Janet, 1980-1985 (Box 6, Folder 384)
    - Meyers, Richard K., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 385)
    - Meyers, Tom and Mary, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 386)
    - Milad, Monet, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 387)
    - Militello, Anne, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 388)
    - Miller A. "Mac", 1970 (Box 6, Folder 389)
    - Miller, Bill, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 390)
    - Miller, Stephen Paul, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 391)
    - Miller, Tom (Tom Verlaine), undated (Box 6, Folder 392)
    - Mills, Criss, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 393)
    - Moore, Marianne, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 394)
    - Moore, Thurston, undated (Box 6, Folder 395)
    - Morris, Richard, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - Mortifoglio, Richard (to Theresa Stern), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 397)
    - Mucha, Patty Basira, 1985-2000 (Box 6, Folder 398)
    - Mueller, Cookie, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 399)
    - Myles, Eileen, 1986-1992 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    - Nable, Eugenie, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 401)
    - Nabakov, Vladimir, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 402)
    - New Directions, 1971-1975 (Box 6, Folder 403)
    - Nilsen, Beate, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    - Noble, Peter, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 405)
    - Noel, Susan, undated (Box 6, Folder 406)
    - Norman, Robert, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 407)
    - Norton, Mark, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - Offutt, Chris, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - O'Keefe, Georgia, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - Olander, Renee, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - Oldenburg, Patty, 1971-1981 (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - Osofsky, Susan, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - P Awards, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - Padgett, Ron, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 415)
    - Palcewski, John, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - Parker, Sylvia, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 417)
    - Patton, Will, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 418)
    - Perez, Omaha, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 419)
    - Perez, Rich, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 420)
    - Perlak, Marianne, undated (Box 6, Folder 421)
    - Perlich, Tim, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 422)
    - Perry, Charles, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 423)
    - Pett, Sukey, undated (Box 7, Folder 424)
    - Pipet, Claire, 1984-2000 (Box 7, Folder 425)
    - Plumley, William, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 426)
    - Plymell, Charles, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 427)
    - Pollé, Amy, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 428)
    - Posset, Benn, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 429)
    - Pound, Ezra, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 430)
    - Prapoulenis, Chuck (KAZ), undated (Box 7, Folder 431)
    - Prausuitz, Maja, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 432)
    - Press, Richard, undated (Box 7, Folder 433)
    - Prost, Celia (to RH), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 434)
    - Prost, Celia (artwork to RH), undated (Box 7, Folder 435)
    - Prost, Celia (from RH), 1990 (Box 7, Folder 436)
    - Prost, Celia (Bard Application), undated (Box 7, Folder 437)
    - Prune, Veronique, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 438)